Kakeru has friends close enough to invite for a sleepover.
Of course, why wouldn't he?
Hey, Sengoku!
Can I have the loft, please?
That's fine, but I still need to tidy it up.
I don't mind a little mess.
It's a lot of mess, not a little.
You really don't have to clean.
That many books cannot be considered safe, so I really do.
It's like a falling rock zone up here.
No way!
Falling rock zones rule!
I love them!
What is with you?
Fine.
I guess if you're okay with it, I can be too.
Good grief.
Such a fuss.
The floor is plenty comfy.
Compared to the loft?
Well, somebody certainly thinks so.
Someone longs like a pearl on the jacket.
No way!
The lights aren't even out!
You're gonna need to scoot down a little, dude.
It is rather cramped.
I'm sorry.
Nah, it's cool.
I'm too hot.
Stop stripping, you dingus!
If the shirt goes, all your hard work goes along with it!
Um, what?
Just tucking them in!
Good night, guys!
See you in the morning.
Sleep sounds so good.
Hmm?
There's no space for me to lie down.
None.
Bye.
Finally.
二人の序章だと意味をくれたこと
きっと知らないだろう 君が呼ぶ僕の名前
由来より大きな意味をくれたこと
飲み干した甘いサイダー 見せ返る僕を笑った
作った笑顔なんかもいらないね
どうしてどうしてもらってばかりいる僕を
愛しいというの僕は何も返して返して
生きて生きるんだろうが
私思いが満ちていく
この感情の名前をそっと
君に捨てるよ 幸せ
バイモータが Overwatch
今の週目が見つかった
味が上がり
匐日会川上げ 海TheseKawa
海田は player
見ます available
いしきげんじん
俺たちのカイプは現れた
君が見つけだ
そこでぉ行くわ
ほい今まもに
鎌田まで回る
この earthだ
おっ becauseです
これは
tinyのか
彼の家が commence
What on this twisted earth are you dreaming?
Wait, that's...
It's just a goldfish.
A goldfish?
And who's Motoko?
Now what?
Never have I been more remorseful for not keeping my room clean.
Looks like an actual pig sleeps in here.
Sheesh, clean it up.
Mom, you were right.
No, wait, it's not messy.
My room's just small.
And it's filled wall to wall with books.
Even Dad puts his books in here.
Of course there's no space to sleep.
It's a miniature library.
Oops, sorry.
Oh, Iora, you okay?
I gotta use the bathroom.
What about you, not tired?
Uh...
Dude, use your words.
We're the ones imposing by crashing here.
I did try, but I felt kind of bad.
All right, gents, wake up and fall in!
Ah!
That's okay, it is, sergeant!
Oh, no.
The president has nowhere to sleep in his own home.
He should have spoken up way sooner.
I'm sorry.
I'll shove the sleeping dead to the TV,
and I'll scooch a little closer to the wall,
and bada-bing, bada-boom, problem solved.
San Goku, can you cut yourself in half by chance?
No.
I know.
Why don't you and Miyamura go sleep in the loft instead of me?
Then I can move down here.
That won't work.
Two people aren't gonna fit up there.
The two of you will.
You guys are each a half.
Two halves make a whole.
Damn.
I hate that logic, but we have no choice.
We're going up, Miyamura!
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Kiyosuke.
But I'm going home today.
Come on!
There is enough room for both of us up here,
but I don't like it.
Stop stripping, you dingus!
Screw the pool.
Oh, I'll go change over there.
Remy accidentally sprayed Miyamura with the hose the other day.
What's weird is he insisted on wearing his sake uniform.
I wonder why.
I left my cell.
Whoopsie!
I'll grab it real quick and leave you...
B.
Uh...
I just remembered.
I snapped my phone in two parts,
then crushed it to powder and washed it all down the drain.
That's right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
It's not what you're thinking!
Please, don't pay me any mind.
No matter what you do,
you'll always be Sengoku to me.
Of course I mind an interpretation like that!
You misread everything!
Stop running away!
Let me explain!
I've seen all I need to see
and have drawn my conclusion.
Save your breath.
I won't be swayed.
It's not good to be so stubborn!
I have the utmost respect for you, Sengoku.
So I do want to hear you out.
But it's just...
Well...
Um...
Use your words, Miyura!
But first, listen!
The only goal I was trying to accomplish
was stripping him,
which I had my reasons for!
That's all I wanted, I swear!
So your only goal was stripping him?
I have the utmost respect for you.
No!
I made it worse!
Okay, let me try again.
I didn't want to take his shirt off,
but wait!
Don't silently...
Homeboy suspicious.
The press doesn't miss much.
You know, Sengoku,
I just realized you can sleep down here.
We've already established
there isn't enough room for three!
Sure, now.
But that changes if you move the table.
We can just stand it on its side.
Shove all those books in a corner somewhere.
How did that solution not occur to me?
So much time was wasted.
You said it.
What happened?
It's too early for...
She was laughing in his sleep
and it freaked me the hell out,
so I hit him.
I was laughing in my sleep
and he's a freak,
so he hit me.
Those don't sound like pleasant ways to wake up.
Nope.
Good morning anyway.
Good morning to you, too.
Yes, good morning.
I feel like I didn't get much sleep.
Miyamura!
Seize the day!
Or keep snoozing.
Man, that guy can sleep.
On our days off from school,
he'll cobs ease till it gets dark out.
That's excessive.
I volunteer to wake him up!
Don't look at me like that!
All I intend to do is get him out of bed!
I volunteer, too!
Miyamura, wake up squad, go!
It doesn't require a squad!
Too late!
I'm going!
Hold up, Shu!
I'll do it!
Get back down here!
It's my loft!
I should do it!
Ah!
Stop!
Yura!
Why?
He's still breathing, guys.
Um, good morning to you, Miyamura.
Yeah, what'd he say?
Morning.
It's morning?
It is.
Why are all of you here watching me sleep?
That is so beside the point!
Bro, can't you see you're in danger?
What danger?
Hey, let's swap.
I'll lead the wake-up squad.
But if we try to trade positions, we might crush him for real.
Shu, keep your butt planted right where it is.
Sengoku's acting like he might pull something, if you know what I mean.
I absolutely will not!
Point the judging stairs somewhere else!
I trust your men, Mr. President.
Yeah, right!
Why are you stuttering, then?
It's too early for this much excitement.
It's your wake-up call, Sleepy.
More like an ambush.
And I need a bathroom.
Back it up, Ishikawa.
Beep, beep, beep!
And give the present opening to get to Miyamura?
I don't think so.
It's a risk I'm willing to take, so please let me through.
I warned you.
It's a long way.
Can you hold it?
Yes, thanks to 18 years of experience.
So, why are you gunning for Miyamura all of a sudden?
Watch how you phrase things, please!
For the record, I was just doing my job as a class representative, okay?
Since when isn't a class rep's job to undress other people in their sleep?
If it's not, but please, please tell me why he hides his skin and saved my curiosity.
I don't understand.
You really want to know?
I'll tell you.
It's a bit of a hike to get to your restroom, Mr. Pre...
What? What's wrong? Who died?
Nobody.
Huh?
I just majorly covered for you.
Is that right?
You can shoot a bazooka out of his solar plexus.
Yeah, uh...
What did you cover? They're talking about a bazooka.
You know, that thing you have.
Even when Remy soaked him with water, he refused to shed his uniform.
Oh.
Miyamura?
Who else would I mean?
That came out of left field, so I wasn't sure.
But yeah, it's a mystery.
Hmm.
A mystery you've already solved, perhaps.
Negatory.
It's cold.
Hey, Prez. Let me warm up in here.
Oh.
What's going on, Ishikawa?
Sup.
Like a Miyamura moth to the flame, here you are.
What? There's no fire.
Come right on in!
You're a little too happy to see me.
Miyamura?
Aren't you hot?
I told you I came because I'm cold.
You'll heat up pretty quick, though.
See how Ishikawa dished his blazer?
That's how toasty he is.
Dude.
How obvious can you be?
He got that warm?
Maybe I'll ditch it a little later.
Blast.
Have I ever seen you in a school sweater before?
I don't own one.
It'd look nice.
Snug in all the red spots.
Hey, why don't you try mine on it, see if you like how it fits you?
You're scaring me.
Here.
Oh, feels legit.
My plan actually worked.
At last, he'll change his clothes and I'll see what he's been hiding.
Miyamura said his tattoos show through a white button down.
He's totally cut onto Sengoku's scheme and is just gonna...
He's gotta be kidding!
Yes!
Take off your sweater!
No, he's gonna find out!
Are you all right?
It's so warm.
And the material for these things is top notch.
How do I look, huh?
Tell me.
You look great!
I really thought today would be the day.
What day?
I'm just gonna come right out and ask.
Why are you so against removing your clothes?
Because I'm rational.
I'm not suggesting you prance around Stark naked.
I meant when you changed for P.E. and stuff.
What's this?
Is the president obsessed with me?
As if!
I just really, really want to know!
Why's that?
It has to go without saying, shouldn't it?
Because it's clearly not normal behavior!
And why's that?
Calm down, Miyamura!
The God President's bullying me!
Ah!
I stole my sweater!
Give it back!
That's a school sweater you have on right now.
Why'd you sprint here, dummy?
Oh, welcome home, son.
Is that a new sweater you're wearing?
He got away.
Let's go.
Before we turn into ice.
Hey, thanks for waiting.
Hmm?
Shall we?
Yeah.
It's freezing.
This recent snow made me realize
spring is still far away.
I'm sorry you have to wear a skirt.
So cold.
Hands.
Huh?
Here.
Yes, Remy.
You're very cold.
Nuh-oh.
Remy's warm.
But I'm cold.
You took the cold for me
and now I'm warm as I can be.
Is that a fact?
Hand.
Yeah, yeah.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Hold my hand, silly!
She's angry?
Walk properly, please.
She feels warm.
Sengoku, you warming up?
Mm-hmm.
Then I guess that only makes one of us.
Remy's hand is still ice cold,
but yours are bony enough to be a skeleton's.
Oh.
You want to let go?
Not at all.
Remy's hands aren't perfect either.
They're tiny.
They're fine.
Do you feel like going somewhere, or...?
Nah.
You picked up the pace.
Because I wasn't paying attention.
Then pay attention.
Right.
Remy wants to walk slower.
Any slower and we would...
Ugh!
Stop.
You're almost home.
Went from freezing cold
to just freezing in place.
What's going on?
Hug.
Uh...
Never mind.
Hug?
Okay.
Yay!
Hug!
Let me have my arms back for a minute, Remy.
Much better.
Kiss.
No.
We're on the street.
I understand.
Good.
Hey, we better get going.
The library's gonna close in five.
Oh!
You're right!
Oh, man.
Remy's head feels like it's gonna explode.
You did use it a lot today.
And you're sure you don't want me to go over your math homework?
Positive.
I can do that assignment by myself.
Think so?
Yep!
Let's go, Sakura!
Sengoku.
Would you like to walk home together?
Sure.
Got everything?
Yeah, I'm good.
You look ready for a blizzard.
Because I'm cold-hearted.
I didn't say that.
Hori, what you looking at?
Huh?
Where's Remy?
Dunno.
It's pretty unusual to see those two by themselves.
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
Hmm...
Well, whatever.
It's not like I spend every waking second with my boyfriend.
Yeah, exactly!
Hey!
Real quick question for you ladies!
Have you seen Sengoku or Sakura?
Huh?
They were here a minute ago, but then Remy went to the bathroom, and now they're gone!
Are you ready for a storm?
You ready for a storm?
The one in my heart.
Well, here and last, I guess!
Oh, what was that for?
Take a guess!
It's fine!
It is!
But hush!
And what if it was like that, but it's not?
Like what?
You weren't hiding something, right?
No.
What would we have to hide?
Hori?
They could have stopped in the student council room.
I'll try giving them a call.
Ah!
I'm okay!
Do you see that over on the window straight across from us?
There's a giant, really weird-looking bug just chilling out!
I want to see the giant bug!
Look!
Leave it to Hori to worry about a problem that doesn't exist.
Hey, boss!
Is the S&C 60?
You're okay?
Sure.
How much trash did you throw away?
Got distracted by the president.
He's here with Kono.
Hmm.
What caught me off guard is Ayasaki's M.I.A.
And the bag that Kono had with her looked like it might be a gift.
Dude!
You spilled everywhere!
Then he's cheating!
Don't jump to conclusions!
Oh!
Ayasaki's on the market again now!
It's my chance.
I repeat, don't jump to conclusions.
And why am I the one cleaning your mess?
You do it!
You would, uh, yep.
Knew that loud voice was yours.
Ah!
I wasn't having shady thoughts!
Huh?
Noticed her sans Ayasaki for today, huh?
Yes, for today.
I'm not sure how to interpret that response.
Don't tell her that I was here.
Oh-ho!
What exactly will happen if I do?
Shut the hell up!
Huh?
Do not tell her I was here.
I'll take it to the grave.
What was that?
See you later.
Bye.
Till tomorrow.
Please don't ask the impossible of me, Sakura!
I've never scored above a 40 in math ever, so it's no go!
Just 60 points!
No!
Hmm, score at least 60, and we'll visit that chocolate shop you like.
We can get...
The premium cookies?
Mm-hmm, yeah, those ones.
Oh, neat to try.
But Remy isn't motivated by material things.
Well, good luck anyway.
Right, next tier we have...
Nice job.
You finally scored higher than a 40 on a test.
Remy said that she isn't motivated by material things.
Huh?
Hmm.
Good morning.
Sakura!
Why did you leave without me yesterday?
Where did you go?
Sorry about that.
I was getting a little...
Sweet treat.
The cookies!
How come Remy got less than a 60 on the milk exam?
Which is irrelevant.
I was just in that area and decided to treat myself.
Wow, you were right.
These are good.
Wait a second.
Remy wants them too, please.
Go right ahead.
I bake my own cookies every once in a while, but it's hard to pass up a nice shop like that.
Thanks, Sakura.
You're awesome.
Hmm?
You say something?
Sure, Dennis!
Oh, okay.
Oh!
We should save some cookies for Sengoku.
No, we shouldn't.
Remy would have that much less if I ate any cookies.
I'm sorry.
It was like we're the real Sengoku.
You freezer!
I don't like that!
You're done the crap job of staying hidden, buddy.
If you suck it up!
Oh, there, there, there.
Yeah, I can't lay it.
Yeah, I can't anda.
手見せびらかしたもの 褒めてくれた君も 前から同じの持っていたの
Wow 今更そんなこと 掘り返さないでよ 眩しすぎた日々を 離したくないの
Ah 何やってんだろう そんな日はさ
ちゃんと前を向いてるよって 言ってくれる君が必要なんだ
Ah また想いが張り裂けそうなのに
URLより短い 言葉にしかできない私です
Ah I'm so sad ここでも 君に飛べるように
出会えるように できてたなら
arkadaşlar
おいしい
おわり